[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Rocky Balboas restaurant?", "correct_answer": "Adrians", "incorrect_answers": ["Rockys", "Mickeys", "Apollos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy movie Planes, Trains  Automobiles, what was the name of the car rental business that rented Steve Martins character a car at the St. Louis airport?", "correct_answer": "Marathon", "incorrect_answers": ["Avis", "Hertz", "Acme"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the anastomotic loop of vessels near the base of the brain.", "correct_answer": "Circle of Willis", "incorrect_answers": ["Zygomatic Process", "Thoracic Circulation", "Portal Circulation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Academy Awards did the 2003 movie The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King win out of eleven nominations?", "correct_answer": "Eleven", "incorrect_answers": ["Nine", "None", "Five"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is better to work out with free weights.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The International Nuclear Events Scale, used to signify the grade of nuclear accidents, has how many levels?", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "3", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This bomber was introduced in February 1955.", "correct_answer": "B-52", "incorrect_answers": ["B-17", "F-15", "B-29"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Princess Protection Program, is Brooke the first to find out Rosies secret?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which American city is the fast-food restaurants chain McDonalds incorporated?", "correct_answer": "San Bernardino, California", "incorrect_answers": ["Phoenix, Arizona", "Oak Brook, Illinois", "Arcadia, California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these living creatures appearred on Earth first?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Reptiles", "Seed plants", "Birds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of what descent is singer and songwriter Duffy, born on 23 June 1984?", "correct_answer": "Welsh", "incorrect_answers": ["Irish", "Australian", "Russian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does a cetologist study?", "correct_answer": "whales", "incorrect_answers": ["wine", "words", "art"]}]